[Music]
Eric it's great to see you Dion long
time man how are you doing really good
man how about you good good I I
appreciate you inviting us uh to to come
and kind of talk about we're doing here
i' I've been looking forward to this
yeah same same well I want to get out of
the way to let you fully take the stage
but thanks so much for coming on and I
can't wait toh to learn about what
you've been up to recently heck yeah
awesome yeah looking forward to sharing
more about us um cool I I guess I can I
can kind of kick off with just a a quick
uh intro on on who I am and what we've
been up to as a company um but so I'm
I'm Eric Sim is the co-founder and CEO
of stock Blitz and I think Dion had
actually mentioned some of the origins
of of uh what we've been doing at stack
Blitz actually before I go further hi
everyone I'd like you I think there's a
chat that you can type into if you're
watching hello I'd love to know where
everyone's punching in from um so feel
free to to to uh you know you pop into
the chat and and and you know give a
greeting Etc um uh you know I started
this company with my uh co-founder uh
you five six seven years ago now and you
really the stackit we've been up to has
been about about allowing the web to be
able to build for the web you know if
you think about every other major
platform uh that's ever existed uh
whether it's uh you know windows with
visual studio and and Mac with uh xcode
every platform uh you know every the
most powerful platforms always have a
built-in capability to build
applications themselves for that
platform and the web you know until
until uh you know we came along did not
have this capability and uh you know
there's certain things like you know Wix
or Squarespace or Cloud ID like Cloud 9
or rep or whatever that like let you
kind of build the web but they're not
actually let they're not running an
actual Dev environment they're not
actually running an IDE where it's
running an operating system inside of
the browser tab itself um they're either
running you know servers on a VM that
you have to pay money to use um or
they're just like a drag and drop
Builder so it's again not actually
leveraging uh your browser itself to to
run a a full powerful Dev environment
and that's really important because if
you want to build amazing applications
you want to have the best tools possible
uh you know for for creating you know
sophisticated web applications not just
a static website or Etc and you want to
be accessible to everyone on the planet
you should be able to open up a browser
Tab and just be able to make something
and uh to dat if we can get my screen
shared I can kind of show you um uh to
dat you know the up until uh 60 days ago
is um the primary way the primary
interface uh to this technology we made
called Web container um was an IDE was
like a vs code based IDE so if I go and
just like click into this little project
here um you'll see it's like this IDE
experience and what's really cool just
to point out is this is a full operating
system here running inside of the
browser so it's not using a cloud BM or
anything it's actually doing this mpm
install running the dev server Etc
entirely inside of the browser tab right
so just like a Google dock or figma I
could send this link to you um you could
open up on your own device Etc and be
actually run this and and edit this
project live on your own device right um
which is really cool but when you kind
of think about you know uh it's actually
rather complicated to use an ID you have
to be you know rather technical to
actually go and and leverage this to
actually build like a real application
right and uh you know what's what's
changed in the past couple of months
here um you know really since the
beginning of the summer is you know AI
models have gotten extremely good at
writing high quality production grade
code um you to the degree where even
folks that uh have never coded before
are you know uh somewhat technical can
actually build full production grade
applications um and so the whole the
whole bit with stack blets has always
been about removing the need to set up a
local environment and and again making
it as easy to open a full Dev
environment in a in a browser tab as it
is to open a figma document or a Google
doc and by merging kind of these latest
Frontier AI models in with the
technology we made um we thought you
know this could be a pretty a pretty
cool experience um that that we could
actually build here that would be
amazing for developers would Excel
accelerate their workflows but also for
folks that are non-developers could
enable them to build production grade
websites like they've never been able to
before um and so actually earlier this
year a little bit of inside baseball we
we had the idea for uh bolt this product
I'll flip over to it um we had the idea
for Bol and um you know basically kind
of the merger if you think like Claud or
chat GPT plus you know if they had
access to an in browser operating system
you know that's the essentially the
pitch of what bolt is we had this idea
earlier this year we we actually tried
building it with some of the frontier
models at the time and they just weren't
good enough uh to to write accurate code
that didn't have bugs or you weren't
hallucinating Etc um and uh you know so
we put this idea on the shelf and then
back I think it was in May or June we
got a sneak peek at some of the latest
stuff that's that's come out since then
and we're like oh oh my god did we this
is this is this it should actually be
possible now to do and the result has
kind of exceeded all expectations we had
of what what you could do with this sort
of tool um but the the response here has
been insane I mean just in the in the
first four weeks we've been online I
think as of today we've been online
seven weeks but just in the first four
weeks um you know we went from zero to
four million of ARR um on this product
and and you know we have hundreds of
thousands of people per week now using
this thing um and so you and we're like
a 20 person team so we've been trying to
keep the lights on over here and and
match the demand um but um so I guess
like enough talking maybe just best to
like show a demo of how this thing works
um so maybe we start with something
simple so like uh you know something
that this thing should absolutely be
able to do and now that I said that
watch you know where the demo gods are
gonna make this thing break not I'm with
that they don't but um you know make a
beautiful to-do out and I'm gonna hit
enter and at this point you know this
kind of looks like chat gbt or claw or
whatever uh this is where it doesn't so
we actually on the right here we
actually have a full IDE environment so
you can actually see it's punching out
the files that we're going to need um
it's h writing all the code that's going
to be need to actually build this
application we hav again the terminal
that's running entirely in the browser
here it's going and installing these
dependencies um it's going and finishing
up making our to-do app and uh within
you know a handful of seconds here we
should see a working to-do app if
everything goes goes well um but uh this
is kind of the the power of this
integrated experience because normally
when you're using CLA or Che gbt uh if
they're punching out good code you have
to like copy and paste it to something
locally um often local idees are you
know they're rather complicated and uh
so you have to be kind of telling it
specifically hey add this file add this
thing whereas with this ouri agent um
can really think holistically about hey
let's build this application from zero
to to actually something that works and
as you can see um we've got a working
to-do app um add one wow and how about
uh you know do live uh
video stream what right now and I'll
check that actually I should uncheck
that we're not done with this video
stream um any pretty cool idea um and
this is uh you know this is just the
start like we you we have we have more
work to do on on this application I can
say you know you know use like a purple
theme I can just kind of tell it to do
anything it'll go ahead and it'll uh
flip back over to the IDE go and make
these changes for us again I don't I
have no idea how this thing works I I
don't I didn't a single line of code in
this application it's going and and
building this thing for me um I'm giving
feedback to it like imag as if I was a a
PM you know or or a manager um and this
agent is going and uh just building
something that's that looks good and
actually really really functions well um
we'll give it a second to to tie up um
and K you this is really the vision of
of what we have for Bal and I think you
know some of the most exciting stuff uh
in the AI agent space is the
consolidation of all the different steps
you normally have to do to get an idea
into your fingertips and get a result
from the you know the computer right and
this I mean this this dramatically cuts
down the the amount of time uh to to get
something real I mean we have you know
look at this this this is pretty
good-looking to-do app right um of
course so we've gone from idea to having
a working app but if I want to use this
somewhere right if I want to you know
buy a domain and get this on production
how to do that well we actually have a
built-in integration um up here if I can
go and zoom in uh all you have to do is
just click this deploy button and we
automatically you don't have to sign in
to netlify we have this integration with
netlify where we do a production build
in your browser again we're running an
operating system here so we can uh you
know just do the build here we'll deploy
that site live we'll get the link back
and we can you know view that link and
if we want to keep it we can attach it
to our netlify account um by clicking
this URL but if we go and click over
here you can see this is a live
production URL of this application right
um and so uh say hello world not Hello
World hello world you know um refresh
and it stays there so this is obviously
a very a very simple example right but
you can kind of Imagine um how how much
of a game changer this is uh in so many
senses like some of the Incredible use
cases we've seen is we have startups
that are building landing pages with
this and even building out like we've
had our you our first startups launch
off of this just in the past seven weeks
there's an a full CRM with a back end
that was built um I mean tons of amazing
full stack production software um that's
been built where these folks have not
even written one line of code and
they've just been prompting uh the AI to
actually make these things um and so uh
anyways this is It's been it's been it's
been an incredible seven weeks of just
seeing uh seeing folks build stuff with
bolt. new I thought one thing that we
kind of to show the power of this um you
know
is this clearly we're moving to a world
now where anyone can have an idea in
spawn
software if whether they have a business
idea or if they just have something that
they themselves need for their own use
case uh one of the things that I made
previously I I did an Iron Man last
month so I created a calculator using
this of like my training the the amount
of running and biking and swimming I was
doing Etc like this kind of deeply
personal software to help me kind of
achieve my goals um I thought kind of a
fun one would be uh why don't we have
this thing make a presentation uh for
this talk um so I'm actually I'm gonna
go ahead and copy and paste in um the uh
the session title and Abstract that we
uh made here I'm gonna say um make a
presentation uh for AI native
Devcon um will be showing bolt. new here
is the info for it um and so that's uh
you
know there's entire classes of just
productivity tools like slides and docks
and you know Etc well we I've actually
not tested this prompt by the way so
we're all going to find out live here
how well this works but uh this can
actually just create productivity
software for you from the ground up
that's that's tailored to your needs um
and uh and so it's going to go ahead and
create a slide deck here wow this
actually extremely fast let's go and see
this thing uh spin up um but um you know
I think that the kind of the the the the
possibilities are endless and that's
what we've been seeing um you know from
the folks that have been that have been
using bold so wow this is incredible
let's go ahead and full screen this
let's see what the presentation is look
at that pretty good even pulls in a
background image um let's go ahead and
uh click to the next Slide the
vision deployment should be instant this
is all true this is all true I I I you
know I could have made this presentation
better myself um absolutely absolutely
yeah should be a natural extension of
your workflow idea deployment in seconds
no setup required everyone should be
able to use this on this planet um
here's a here's an a diagram of of how
this works um to help us all understand
this uh so what is Bolt thought new
anyways you get the idea it's this is
um I'm spe speechless right I mean this
is this is
crazy you know and the incredible thing
is I can go in here and just and I can
tell that AI hey you know change uh
slide three to say da da da and it'll
just do it right um it's it's like
having not just a pair of programmer
next to you but it's like having an
extension of yourself to just go and and
uh not just like build web apps and
landing pages but build things for you
uh in your everyday life right um any
I'll go and kind of you know minimize
this again but uh kind of unbelievable
uh the sort of the sort of applications
that you can build with this thing um so
I think um you know that's that's kind
of the the high level of like what you
can do with bolt. new and of course you
know for folks that are like to go back
to like the the to-do application um you
know this the the future that we that we
are seeing here and that we envision is
is not that developers are going away
you like with every technology that's
ever existed uh there's there's always
been this kind of question and concern
of you know okay well what's what's
going to happen what's going to happen
to people that uh ride horses when Cars
come out you know it's like the world
adapts and changes and people are able
to leverage the new technology um to
really go and build the future in a way
that just wouldn't have been possible
before it's just and it's a better
future and I I really truly believe that
that's going to be the case here where
you have developers that are leveraging
these AI tools to augment their
workflows to augment their ability to go
and build amazing applications so it's
actually more important than ever to
have sophisticated really uh brilliant
engineers in the world um that are that
are able to not spend their time on
things that are you know monotonous and
mundane but really on extremely
creative difficult uh challenges to
solve right and so to that end one of
the really cool things is because our of
our Origins as an IDE company you any
bolt project actually seamlessly ties in
with the stacks IDE so I can actually
click to open this project in stack
blitz so I can actually do you know code
editing here like in a very direct way
of course you can actually edit by the
way in in Bolt you can actually go in
and edit files directly in here as well
but you want to have like the full IDE
experience like push to get etc etc um
you know you get all of that in these
stack Blitz IDE that's powered by vs
code and whatnot and when you hit save
you can actually just click back to
reopen this back and Bol so you can keep
prompting with this sort of experience
um and so I think I think for us it's
you know the way that we that we you
know where this is going and just for us
and and you know kind of the industry in
general um is people that are uh you
know developers are only going to get
more powerful and they and they're going
to get to be able to build um even more
amazing things that wouldn't have been
possible for them to do before you know
strictly from even just a how much time
it would take um the the cognitive
complexity of managing all these things
but but along with that this Rising tide
is Raising all boats and and and to a
degree that people that are not even
technical that have never coded before
can actually be a part of this they can
actually be a part of of kind of
rewriting the the the world's software
order so to speak uh and build things
for themelves their families other folks
um in a way that is so much simpler than
a lot of the things that previously
existed if you think of the you know
what are your current options today for
someone who's non-technical to to build
a website you're looking at uh you know
there's a lot of website Builders out
there like Wix or Squarespace and what
we're what you know we're seeing folks
that are opting for this experience over
that which was initially a little
surprising but it actually makes sense
like the these website builder tools are
actually rather complicated to use you
have to learn how to drag and drop these
things and choose a template and this
and this and this and that and then you
have to like type in all the words and
stuff yourself you can come here and say
I want you know I want a website for my
wedding uh it's on this date Etc hit
enter boom you have something that's
live um you know on production right so
anyways that's uh that's the the short
um you know of what we're up to with
bolt you kind of where we see things
going and i' I've seen a lot of
questions uh in the comments so far so I
I figur maybe uh maybe we take a little
time I can we can answer some questions
I'm also happy to do some more demos if
folks want to see stuff but um yeah
maybe is a good good pause point and
kind of hammer through some of these
that sounds great let's do it there's
definitely a lot of questions um which
is awesome and just shows how uh excited
people are about uh these things um and
so guy actually asked how big an
application do you think uh can be built
this way uh kind of today and and
tomorrow and I'm curious what you've
seen already and and as you think about
evolving things where it can go yeah
totally I mean we have seen I mentioned
there's there's someone who actually
built an entire CRM platform with this
and had the CRM platform has a built an
AI chatbot and like it's it's very
sophisticated it's got like a calendar d
da um so which has been kind of
mindblowing because it you know we I
suppose we knew that that was possible
but we didn't uh we didn't expect this
to happen so quickly and I think today
that you know a lot of power users are
building stuff to that degree uh every
day um you know we're I think that for
our team what we are actually doing is
figuring out okay how do we make it even
easier to build stuff of that size and
scale within the product um and really
make it smooth because to to kind of get
there there's you know you have to like
really really start learning more and
more about the tool um you know so
there's I think there's probably a drop
off of of folks that want to build
something that sophisticated but there's
actually really no technical no
meaningful technical limitation around
it's really more kind of user experience
stuff and you know some some under the
stuff Plumbing um but I mean there's
there's uh I mean what you would kind of
deem as hey this is a startup a real
startup with a real production
application there's there's dozens of
those that have come out already um and
so I think I think you fast forward you
know one two three four
months I would not be surprised to see a
a meaningful shift in like uh startups
building their first MVPs to you know
contining to build it you know going
forward i i i i Bolter tools like both I
think will become a pretty common way
that that's happening
so got it that's great M's asking this
looks amazing it looks like it's easy to
check uh requirement specs visually met
um what about the code
itself yeah so um yeah to so great
question so today you know regarding the
code itself um you like one of the nice
things is this is a full Dev environment
so you can actually say write a a test
suite for this that does these things
Etc and and you you can actually hook
into those test Sues and make sure it's
actually uh adhering to them Etc
regarding like memory leaks and that
sort of thing I think this is kind of
the long tale of this where you know
there's like this 8020 that we're
hitting now or going to be hitting you
know in the next month or two or
something like that then there's the
Last Mile of this which is okay and then
as this thing is existing in a
production environment how are we
helping you debug errors that come up
with memory leaks or this or that um and
and even even just uh so one of the
things we've been talking with the
Chrome Dev tools folks about is just as
uh folks are building with bolt because
it's all running in the browser uh
Chrome Dev tools has access to all the
information you would ever want or need
uh about memory leaks happening um and
so that's something that you
theoretically we could of uh exfiltrate
from chrome Dev tools and and you know
feed into our agent to actually process
and catch these sorts of things um and
so a lot of the game is just really
around uh how do you instrument this in
a in a high quality way where there's a
signal and not just a ton of noise or
something um but uh so that's that's
kind of the longtail stuff we have to
work on you know over the over the
coming months um and which will matter
especially for stuff that's going to be
production gr versus I'm building a
landing page or a marketing uh website
or you know something like
that got it uh so you you showed
deployment this question was asked
before you showed that are there other
aspects of the software life cycle that
you're thinking that you want to add
things into the product to to help with
totally yeah I think I think deployment
you know obviously probably one of the
biggest ones we're going to have a g
integration I think that was maybe one
of the other comments um today you can
push to get from stack blits but not
from with bolt within bolt um that's
like probably one of the top requested
features that's now on the docket for us
um so any you all of your typical life
cycle hooks that happen you know uh with
your CI Etc this will just kind of plug
directly into those things I think one
of the cool areas you can imagine is um
with a tool like this often you may have
other stakeholders whether it's
designers or uh you know business
oriented folks or whatever have you that
are part of the stlc process for hey
what are we shipping or how does this
look or how does it function getting
feedback you know Etc and and um there's
something pretty interesting I think
around what if they can just get access
to this and and kind of prompt it
instead of hey can you make the button
blue you know it's
like tell it here's the link you know um
stuff like that I think uh it's it's
it's kind of like a thing where you can
comment on stuff I mean this just takes
to a different level right um so I think
stuff like that I think uh is super
interesting as far as saying this like
someone having them be able to kind of
come into a collaborative workspace
where they're not just telling like
commenting to give some other person
instruction they can actually just tell
the allm to do something and developer
can then look at that and go yep okay it
looks good to me click you know so
that's awesome uh so here's someone
who's a user been using it for a few
weeks and uh they're coming from this I
imagine that this is a common thing too
being a backend Dev that it's like now
I've got superpowers I don't have to ask
my frontend team to do things yet um I
think they're wondering about just
different Integrations with
uh like open a API specs to be able to
just like hand the front end these
different specs of the back end or gra
ql or whatever it is if you envision any
kind of future you know tooling there
that could enable it easy to plug these
together oh yeah absolutely I mean I
think as far as the the API SP I think
that 100% that is the move um the person
who put put that comment up here that is
that is totally the way you should do it
um we actually next week we're
announcing it's it's it's it's released
we just haven't announced it uh we have
a a file we have a a prompt file uh
that's in like if you go tobolt prompt
in the file system um you can edit that
and anything in there will be every time
you open up a chat with the thing that
will be hydrated into the conversation
as context that it's aware of so uh I
would recommend taking your API spec
popping into there I mean try and
shorten the spec as much as possible so
you're not uh you're spending less money
uh you know per message with the context
but um that way uh it'll be 100% aware
of how your API is set up and um and and
it can can go and build the endpoints
that it needs to or not build the end
points sorry build the code to access
your end points um Etc but that's that's
one of the beautiful things about this
it it is PL if you have a custom
component system your Custom Design
system you have custom apis like you can
just feed it in and it'll just it'll
just adapt to it you know yeah that's
awesome so this is a good question
around like you talk about kind of
source control of you know the code
itself but being able to do things like
database migrations and other kind of
steps that you want to kind of migrate
and and dat that maybe outside of just
the prompting the system I want it the
button to go from Blue to Red uh how
would folks kind of think about those
parts of evolving totally yeah this is
and we're actually kind of getting this
now because folks are using things like
Firebase and super base for the backends
um and so right now what it does is
it'll actually give you instructions on
how to run migrations I think in the
case of super base uh it'll it'll give
you like something you can even copy
paste and then like you know over into
super base and Etc um what we're
actually doing is we're working on just
direct Integrations with both of those
and and likely other ones in the future
where um bolt is just aware of of the
database the current structure
Etc um and uh and so it can observe that
and then we we have a direct access uh
from within bolt itself to run
migrations or make snapshots or this or
that um and so I think that's that I
think that's where this is gonna I think
it's gonna be a huge unlock I if you can
come here and say I guess like kind of
the key vision for this is is like you
can come here say hey I have an idea for
an app it's like oh do you have a domain
yet no okay cool we've got that um you
know let's go build the app let's set up
a database okay we need to migrate the
database no problem let's go a and do da
da so yeah it's I think every part of
that we want to um you know to the
degree that it's possible you know go
and and make that completely slippery
magic automatic you know yeah got it uh
I'm gonna sneak one in here actually so
you've had this like crazy amount of
usage you know pop up um and so you're
able to see all of these amazing things
that people have been building
have you been able to kind of use that
data and usage to be able to kind of get
quality data that you can then use to
get a feed feedback loop going to make
bo. new better
itself yeah absolutely yeah it's um yeah
yes there's more there's more uh uh you
know we're kind of bringing on our first
uh analytics engineer SL just growth
your GTM engineer sort of person to to
help us even dig into this more we've
we've gotten a ton of qualitative
feedback our team's been talking the
users um a ton and uh so the past seven
weeks we've been kind of running the
gauntlet just ingesting feedback fixing
things improving the product Etc um and
so a lot of what I've kind of spoken to
has been kind of our learnings um from
that that end of things and um uh so I
guess yeah the short short answer is
yeah I think I think the main the main
things we're focused on now there's been
a lot of just kind of pzero stuff just
fixing obvious bugs and limitations um
you know and making it you know
optimizing token usage so people can get
more messages uh per dollar that sort of
thing um the next things we're looking
at are really around the okay now if I'm
building things that are going to be
really production grade those workflows
like making those really really really
amazing um to use and uh and that's like
Integrations with these kind of back end
as a service providers uh git um even
things around collaboration Etc I think
that's going to be that's that's gonna
be a lot of our Focus um you going
forward here for the coming you know
couple of months at
least makes sense uh llms are changing
all the time lots of different ones
they're always upgrading and making
changes how do you how do you think
about that how do you you know kind of
evaluate what's what's going on in this
messy world that's a good question um
because what we found uh is that the eal
benchmarks for Coen are are they may
have been useful a year ago so stuff was
you know needed to improve to a certain
point but they're not representative of
um building real world apps and not
hallucinating on on you know actual
libraries that are out there and that
sort of thing there're not as far as
there's really not any good benchmarks
what's kind of funny is we open source
the uh funny SL inspiring and cool uh is
that we open source the core components
of Bolt so you can kind of like take
bolt and like and web containers and you
know Fork it and build your own and
people have been adding different models
on and so bolt has kind of become uh for
those who that were uh in you were in PC
gaming in like the 2000s like where it's
like does it run crisis you know that
that was kind of the the the gold
standard of like how good is your GPU or
whatever right people are are now saying
okay but this new model came out like
can it run bolt how well does it run
bolt so people will take it down they
they put into bolt they give it a prompt
they go H this thing not that good so
it's it's kind of interesting like this
bolts one of the first real world
production AI apps that's where kind of
the core of its open source you can
actually just test it against stuff and
and usually within a prompter to you'll
find out you you'll find out how good
these things actually are at a real
world test versus just some sort of
specific benchmark you know yeah it's
kind of amazing when I opened up some of
the evals and saw that like so many of
them are focused on like here one line
of code missing does the llm pudding the
right which isn't what developers
actually do all day right it's not like
we're in this almost perfect State all I
have to do is add this one line of code
so I feel like most of the evals are
maybe not to your point doesn't that's
why it doesn't map to real world very
well it's like they're actually
measuring this very weird state of I've
got a jigo puzzle I'm just missing one
piece which isn't obviously totally I
think it's I think very it's probably
extremely useful as as you know we the
ramp over the past couple of years to
measure Coden but I we we're we've hit
we've hit a Tipping Point and that's
like again like the why bolt has been
able to exist right now is that AI Cod
gen has hit a point where you can write
real production grade code and now and
there there as far as you know what
we've seen there just there there's not
yet a good way to quantify that um the
best way is actually to qualify it by
plugging it into a production grade app
like bu and go okay is this G is this
giving me back an app that like looks
good and actually functions and knows
the correct libraries to use Etc um and
so as I suspect we we're we're pretty
excited about this stuff that's been
happening in the open source side
because um you we're seeing there's a
lot of people that have been
contributing to um uh our our open
source stuff and different forks and
whatever hob you and uh it seems like it
it may could play an important role here
in um helping folks that are making
models uh and fine-tuning models to give
them a common Target to say okay how how
do we make it better work it better in
in this sort of real world context you
know got speaking of Open Source Geo
asked about the separation of the open
source side and the commercial side and
someone else asked about kind of the
pricing in general yeah totally yeah so
for for uh how we think about the
commercial side we had no idea that the
uptake that was going to happen on bolt
so we put both out at the same time
we're like hey you know we have two
businesses at stack Blitz you know we
kind of did a dual B similar to like
anthropic or or AI where they have their
chat product and then their API product
stacklist has the same thing with bolt
and with selling our web container uh
Service as an API where you you can get
in browser compute but also all the
networking to mpm and getting whatever
you know built into it um and so for the
open source side like we're we're stoked
to see folks picking this up because I
mean we we are kind of taking our
learnings and backporting them uh you
know soon we're gonna be kind of
backporting a lot of the stuff that
we've been working over the past couple
of weeks but the open source world's
doing a ton of innovation as well and so
uh they're trying out different models
they're trying out different approaches
and um and so it's you know I think it's
just net great for I mean everyone in
this space uh to just see you know all
the different models being you know used
and how to actually leverage them the
best Etc um and uh so on the bolt side
of things you know our pricing is uh you
we have different tiers based of how
much usage you want in a given month so
I thing is it starts at two $20 and goes
all the way up to 200 if you're using
this thing like every single day to like
punch out websites for clients or you
know whatever have you um but any that's
kind of the split uh of our stuff and
the open source side is really important
I think it's uh we invest a lot in open
source generally at stack Blitz even
before bolt um and so having the open
source world uh picking this thing up
and and you know pushing it to different
different and new limits is great for us
and great for everyone else too you
know
yeah and you talked a little bit about
this when I asked about using the the
data side of it but I've also been
curious about you've got all of these
you know prompts and chats and different
things kind of coming in are you
actually using llms to be able to do the
analysis like how do you with so much
coming in at you at this point how do
you even learn what people are using it
for and and and the like totally yeah I
think I think for us what we've been
really what we've been very focused on
is the people that are seeing the most
success with the
product um really spending time with
them and and and them showing us their
prompts and stuff and like in their
General approach of how are you getting
this to really punch out what you want
because there's a lot of people that
that will come to it and they kind of um
they have this this uh uh wrong
impression that this is like the you
know the the genie from a lab where you
kind of say I want this and then boom
you know it's there right and which is
understandable because there's a lot of
hype around AI stuff so people are like
oh like okay I can just type anything
and then they're very disappointed when
it doesn't work um and so what we what
what strikes me as really important is
the the folks that are power users
seeing great success and are really uh
you know masterfully controlling these
llms to to punch out amazing software
kind of uh almost like reverse
engineering what what's going on in in
that person's head and and like how do
we actually build that into the product
how are we like how can they can can we
be prompting the user for certain types
of information kind of catch when
they're trying to do something that is
not maybe going to yield them the best
result you know it's like it's it's very
and this is like the frontier of you
know of you know of research on how do
you how do you how do you build a
technical product for non-technical
folks right um and so any I think we're
spending a lot of time understanding how
the most successful folks using and
trying to like actually build some of
that knowledge into the product itself
so that um it just makes it better for
everyone and there's a really slippery
path for
everyone that's awesome well Eric thank
you so much like you mentioned you've
been involved you know in open source a
lot with all of the the work that you've
done with vit and sponsoring them and
the web containers work that you've done
so uh you know even from the beginning
of your company like you've always
really invested in uh open source even
before Bol and it it's just really great
to see how this is just kind of like
burst onto the scene and just one of the
things I love about programming is the
fun aspect of it and this this is
something that's fun to use I enjoy
using it it's awesome to to see that so
thanks so much for joining us and and
showing this to uh to everyone and um
you know we'll be for folks who have
more questions we we'll be watching for
that on the Discord and but thanks so
much for the time really appreciate it
thank you really appreciate it awesome
all right have a good one see you soon